{
    "levels":{
        "1":{
            "Problem": "The mice eaters",
            "Hint": "Starts with C",
            "Ans": "CAT"
        },
        "2":{
            "Problem": "Opposite of above",
            "Hint": "Starts with B and ends with W",
            "Ans": "BELOW"
        },
        "3":{
            "Problem": "A nutrient-rich liquid food produced by the mammary glands of mammals",
            "Hint": "Starts with M",
            "Ans":"MILK"
        },
        "4":{
            "Problem": "Satellite of Earth",
            "Hint": "Starts with M",
            "Ans": "MOON"
        },
        "5":{
            "Problem": "King of the jungle",
            "Hint": "Starts with L",
            "Ans": "LION"
        },
        "6":{
            "Problem": "Opposite of beautiful",
            "Hint":"Starts with U",
            "Ans": "UGLY"
        },
        "7":{
            "Problem": "National bird of India",
            "Hint": "Starts with P and ends with K",
            "Ans": "PEACOCK"
        },
        "8":{
            "Problem": "Opposite of dark",
            "Hint": "The natural agent that stimulates sight and makes things visible",
            "Ans": "LIGHT"
        },
        "9":{
            "Problem": "Causing laughter or amusement",
            "Hint": "Starts with F and ends with Y",
            "Ans": "FUNNY"
        },
        "10":{
            "Problem": "Largest planet in solar system",
            "Hint":"Starts with J and ends with R",
            "Ans": "JUPITER"
        },
        "11":{
            "Problem": "Opposite of dead",
            "Hint": "Starts with A",
            "Ans": "ALIVE"
        },
        "12":{
            "Problem": "Country with naional anthem 'Jana Gana Mana'",
            "Hint": "This country is also called Hindustan",
            "Ans": "INDIA"
        },
        "13":{
            "Problem": "Who developed numbers based on letters of the alphabet",
            "Hint":"Starts with G",
            "Ans":"GREEKS"
        },
        "14":{
            "Problem": "The mammal which sleeps for 22 hours a day",
            "Hint":"Starts with K and ends with A",
            "Ans": "KOALA"
        },
        "15":{
            "Problem": "National game of India",
            "Hint": "Starts with H and ends with Y",
            "Ans": "HOCKEY"
        },
        "16":{
            "Problem": "Name of the dog which went into space in Sputink-2",
            "Hint": "Starts with L",
            "Ans": "LAIKA"
        },
        "17":{
            "Problem": "In which field of science has Einstein had major impact",
            "Hint": "Starts with P",
            "Ans": "PHYSICS"
        },
        "18":{
            "Problem": "Opposite of export",
            "Hint": "Starts with I",
            "Ans": "IMPORT"
        },
        "19":{
            "Problem": "Picture composed of a variety of mterials pasted on to a surface",
            "Hint": "Starts with C",
            "Ans": "COLLAGE"
        },
        "20":{
            "Problem": "Capital of South Korea",
            "Hint":"Starts with S and ends with L",
            "Ans": "SEOUL"
        },
        "21":{
            "Problem": "National game of Australia",
            "Hint": "Starts with C",
            "Ans": "CRICKET"
        },
        "22":{
            "Problem": "First mathematician of India",
            "Hint": "Inventor of zero",
            "Ans": "ARYABHATTA"
        },
        "23":{
            "Problem": "National flower of India",
            "Hint": "Starts with L",
            "Ans": "LOTUS"
        },
        "24":{
            "Problem": "Where is the days and nights equal",
            "Hint": "A corresponding line on a planet or other body",
            "Ans":"EQUATOR"
        },
        "25":{
            "Problem": "Kidney is an example of",
            "Hint":"Starts with O",
            "Ans": "ORGAN"
        },
        "26":{
            "Problem": "Lightning conductors are made up of",
            "Hint": "It is a good conductor of electricity",
            "Ans": "COPPER"
        },
        "27":{
            "Problem": "5th to 6th centuries AD old 'Elephant caves' located in which state of India",
            "Hint": "Main language of the state is Marathi",
            "Ans": "MAHARASHTRA"
        },
        "28":{
            "Problem": "Opposte of full",
            "Hint": "It even means containing nothing",
            "Ans": "EMPTY"
        },
        "29":{
            "Problem": "Which synthetic fibre is known as artificial silk",
            "Hint": "Starts with R",
            "Ans": "RAYON"
        },
        "30":{
            "Problem": "Which is the first calculating device",
            "Hint": "Starts with A",
            "Ans": "ABACUS"
        },
        "31":{
            "Problem": "What is the name of the software that allows us to browse the internet",
            "Hint": "Starts with B",
            "Ans": "BROWSER"
        },
        "32":{
            "Problem": "What is the name of the process when the operating sytem runs",
            "Hint": "Starts with B and ends with G",
            "Ans": "BOOTING"
        },
        "33":{
            "Problem": "A word for expressing astonishment or admiration",
            "Hint": "It's a palindrome",
            "Ans": "WOW"
        },
        "34":{
            "Problem": "'Ice Hockey' is the national sport of which country",
            "Hint": "It is also kown as land of cakes",
            "Ans": "SCOTLAND"
        },
        "35":{
            "Problem": "Which festival is celebrated in India as festival of colours",
            "Hint": "Starts with H",
            "Ans": "HOLI"
        },
        "36":{
            "Problem": "What is the natinal heritage animmal of India",
            "Hint": "This animmal is killed the most for their tusks",
            "Ans": "ELEPHANT"
        },
        "37":{
            "Problem": "In which state of India is the International kite festival celebrated",
            "Hint": "This country has India's largest coastline",
            "Ans": "GUJARAT"
        },
        "38":{
            "Problem": "Tripitakas are sacred book of",
            "Hint": "They are the followers of Buddha",
            "Ans": "BUDDHISTS"
        },
        "39":{
            "Problem": "Gautama Buddha was born in which country",
            "Hint": "Starts with N",
            "Ans": "NEPAL"
        },
        "40":{
            "Problem": "The first ever Pan India movie was create in which language",
            "Hint": "Lot of people pronounce name of this language as 'Kannad'. Don't forget to add 'a' while writing solution",
            "Ans": "KANNADA"
        }
    }
}